ghost.cc 2011-09-01

# Ghostcc - Privacy Policy

|   
---  

|   
---  
|  |   |  | 

Privacy Policy  
  
---|---|---  
|   
---  
|  |   | **1-  Your Personal Information** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
When you register to receive Ghost Services, you provide Ghost with personally identifiable information (name, address, phone number, email address, age, gender, etc. as well as data that you upload to Ghost or create on Ghost such as files, e-mails and instant messages) and when you use Ghost Services, you automatically provide us with additional information such as your IP address, preferences, transactions and areas of interest. Such information, in the event that it is not publicly available and that you do not ask us to publish it, shall hereinafter be referred to as "Personal Information". It is your duty to provide us with accurate and complete Personal Information and to update your Personal Information whenever necessary or desired. 

Ghost will, as an integral part of its Services and operation, collect and store your Personal Information (on computers owned by Ghost or at data center or storage facilities rented by Ghost). Ghost will use commercially reasonable efforts to keep all Personal Information confidential (for example by requiring username and password before displaying Personal Information, by including a Captcha test in registration and by using a firewall to hinder circumvention) and will use it and deliver it to third parties only in compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the  Ghost Terms of Service.

Ghost may, from time to time and at its sole discretion, revise and update this Privacy Policy. Any updates or revisions will be prominently displayed on Ghost's web site (typically at Privacy policy) along with a link to the updated "Privacy Policy". Ghost may also provide certain services under a different privacy policy which will be clearly indicat ed when registering for or using that Service.   

|  |   | **2-  Ghost Usage of Personal Information** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
We will not rent, sell or share your Personal Information other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. 

We may use the Personal Information we collect to improve our Services. By using Ghost's Services you agree that Ghost may use the Personal Information for research and analysis purposes, to contact you, to provide additional Services, to personalize and customize the Services you use and the content you receive including advertisement, to ensure the quality of our Services and, in an anonymous manner, in preparation of reports to our third party providers or clients.   

|  |   | **3-  Third Party Providers** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
Ghost provides Services using, among other things, various third party service providers. You acknowledge that such third party providers may require Ghost to transfer certain personal information as a prerequisite to providing the Services to a Ghost user. Therefore by choosing to register for a Service embedded, passed through or otherwise linked to by Ghost and provided by a third party, you consent that Ghost may do any of the following:   

  * Deliver your Personal Information to the third party provider.
  * Deliver updates to your Personal Information to the third party provider, from time to time, at its sole discretion or as requested by the third party.
  * Receive certain Personal Information from such third party providers, subject to the terms of their privacy policies and this Privacy Policy.

You acknowledge that Ghost does not control your Personal Information once it has been delivered to third parties and that such third parties will generally have their own privacy policies that may be substantially different than Ghost's Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the respective reputation and privacy policies of such third parties before you choose to use their services and to make your own assessment of the value and risks of using those services. You understand that by the nature of Ghost's service, even if a third party is offering services which are embedded or passed through by Ghost, Ghost may have no commercial relationship with the third party. Moreover, Ghost will usually not have vetted the third party and may even have no knowledge of the third party's existence.   
   
|  |   | **4-  Personal Content** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
As part of our Services, you will be provided with memory space in order to save and manage the files you create and modify and your communications (such as email, instant messaging, documents, etc.). Such content, in case it is specifically marked as "private" by you in accordance with Ghost's Terms of Service, shall hereinafter be referred to as "Personal Content". 

We will not disclose or transfer your Personal Content to third parties in full or in part (other than for purposes of general statistical analysis of the words or content) except 

  * To trusted storage subcontractors of Ghost.
  * To providers of hosted viewers, editors and converters and other hosted tools which help you to create and use the files (whom however may treat your Personal Content in accordance with their own policies and you are strong encouraged to study their privacy policy, other terms and policies and their reputation before using such services).
  * At your request (e.g. if you choose sharing options or to launch a third party provider service with respect to your Personal Content or choose to post Personal Content in a forum which is shared or public).

In addition, we will not expose your Personal Content to humans except at your specific request or where it is reasonably required for data center administration or support functions.   
   
|  |   | **5-  Disclosure of Personal Information and Personal Content** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
In addition to the provisions of the previous section, Ghost may deliver your Personal Information or Personal Content to third parties under the following circumstances:   

  * If obliged by any applicable law or regulation, if ordered by a court of competent jurisdiction, or to protect Ghost's legal interests.
  * In the event necessary, in our opinion and as required or permitted by law, in order to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Ghost, our third party providers and business partners, our users, or the public.
  * Provision of Personal Information to third parties such as contractors and agents providing services to Ghost or on behalf of Ghost under a confidentiality agreement or under another agreement which includes privacy provisions. While such third parties will use the Personal Information to provide services to Ghost or to provide you with services on behalf of Ghost, such third parties will not have the right to use the Personal Information for other purposes or otherwise share the Personal Information.

|  |   | **6-  Credit Card or Payment Information** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
For certain Services and to finalize transactions, we will request your credit card or other payment account information ("Credit Information") which we will maintain in a secure server or in encrypted form. Although, certain Services you may wish to use and acquisitions you may make using Ghost or using third party Services you subscribe to or access via Ghost will require the transfer of your Credit Information to third parties, we will not provide your Credit Information to any third party unless and until specifically authorized by you to do so.   
   
|  |   | **7-  Commercial Content** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
In order to finance Ghost's Services (many of which are free to the user), we may display and deliver targeted advertisement and promotional material to you based on your Personal Information and targeting criteria we receive from our advertising clients. We may pass Anonymous Personal Information (for example zip code, year of birth or preferences without any identification such as name, address, phone number) to third party providers and advertisers (even if you have not specifically subscribed to their services via Ghost) and they may use this in addition to personal information they collect directly in a similar manner, all based on their respective privacy policies.  
   
|  |   | **8-  Cookies** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer that may contain information about you, your computer, your browser, your actions on the web, etc. We may set and access cookies on your computer to improve our Services by, among other things, storing your preferences, your password if you ask us to do so, and a record of which physical computers you use. 

The third party providers and advertisers we work with may also use cookies and we will allow them to set and access cookies on your computer. We have no control over such third party providers' use of cookies and we encourage you to review the privacy policy and reputation of such third party providers before you choose to use their services and to make your own assessment of the value and risks of using those services.   

|  |   | **9-  Solicitation, Collection, Usage & Disclosure of Personal Information of Children** |    
---|---|---|---  
   
Ghost will never knowingly request, collect, use and/or disclose personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we receive actual knowledge that a user or visitor to Ghost is under the age of 13, we will remove all personally identifiable information about that person from our files. In addition, we offer parents reasonable access to information collected from their children, including the opportunity to correct or remove such information.
